Girls Just Want to Have Fun
I come home in the morning light
My mother says when you gonna live your life right?
Oh mother dear we're not the fortunate ones
And girls they want to have fun oh girls just want to have fun
The phone rings in the middle of the night
My father yells what you gonna do with your life?
Oh daddy dear you know you're still number one
But girls they want to have fun oh girls just want to have
That's all they really want some fun
When the working day is done oh girls they want to have fun
Oh girls just want to have fun
Some boys take a beautiful girl and hide her away from the rest of the world
I want to be the one to walk in the sun
Oh girls they want to have fun oh girls just want to have
That's all they really want some fun
When the working day is done oh girls they want to have fun
Oh girls just want to have fun
They just wanna
Oh girls
Girls just want to have fun
Ooh They just wanna
They just wanna
Oh girls
Girls just want to have fun when the workin' when the workin' day is done
Oh when the workin' day is done oh girls girls just want to have fun
Ooh ooh
They just wanna
Oh girls
Yeah girls just want to have fun
When the workin' when the workin' day is done
Girls just want to have fun